{
    "homeworks": [
        {
            "id": "857245aa-e9da-4670-80ca-3265644286ab",
            "name": "Homework 2021/04/19 2",
            "__class": "Homework",
            "__ver": "1",
            "status": "new",
            "tasks": [
                {
                    "id": "a2bfb880-3697-4ce6-99a1-951253a757d4",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 8,
                    "problem": "4 + 4"
                },
                {
                    "id": "a76b16a0-0d34-4d0e-8c3a-3191bb2c7e11",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 9,
                    "problem": "6 + 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "c4fbe184-b87e-4dcb-aa5d-8b6b20464f86",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 5,
                    "problem": "0 + 5"
                },
                {
                    "id": "efb27d77-8ea9-429d-91f0-bfdd6b03df8a",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 3,
                    "problem": "1 + 2"
                },
                {
                    "id": "a481e57d-2c6c-4f5f-8940-e27f9ad3ffc1",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 4,
                    "problem": "7 - 3"
                },
                {
                    "id": "bde47d8a-c06b-4fb4-9a0f-c01f919f404d",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 6,
                    "problem": "7 - 1"
                },
                {
                    "id": "46145cdb-68f6-4d6b-83f0-618d9f5d927f",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 2,
                    "problem": "4 - 2"
                },
                {
                    "id": "127a69f5-81bb-4be5-a29f-1fa045c0a19d",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 12,
                    "problem": "2 + 10"
                },
                {
                    "id": "9cb5f8fd-83b0-45c5-b1d7-f316626b776b",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 11,
                    "problem": "2 + 9"
                },
                {
                    "id": "fc994a07-2839-4c0a-946a-886664dc494b",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 15,
                    "problem": "9 + 6"
                },
                {
                    "id": "df53971f-24c1-4dfb-846e-777e34860a2f",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 14,
                    "problem": "4 + 10"
                },
                {
                    "id": "c48d7285-b3f8-46e5-9d51-e6cfa80e45bc",
                    "type": "none",
                    "__class": "ArythmeticsTaskDef",
                    "__ver": "1",
                    "correctAnswer": 18,
                    "problem": "9 + 9"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}